[Music]
[Applause]
welcome
agency kickoff
[Music]
nothing is impossible I always believed
in not
[Music]
and this new king we need to be stronger
we have to believe that we will be
better will be faster will be better
than everybody else
that's what we want
such an honor to speak to all of our
leaders and Flanders who are here FWD we
are a new we are a differentiated kind
of students company and we know by heart
it's in our DNA that our mission is to
change the way people feel about
insurance
[Music]
[Applause]
we're now leveraging two new
technologies as a way to design greater
customer experience for your customers
along
we are putting the customers first
what's in it for the customer so why do
we choose it do you want is to increase
protection for customers and and make a
better version of yourselves
let us all be part of this wonderful FWD
journey so get ready to get is 30
because disturbance is still good hard
lead to positive change
[Applause]
we FWD we shall be the whole of MDR easy
like that we even declare that effed up
into these are home or believe manners
me coming to Philippines you are my
family and we are one strong family
[Applause]